<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>hotels &#8211; Vocal Travels</title>
	<atom:link href="https://vocaltravels.com.ng/category/hotels/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://vocaltravels.com.ng</link>
	<description>Providing Assured Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 19:52:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Best International Markets in Nigeria for Mini Importation Business</title>
		<link>https://vocaltravels.com.ng/best-international-markets-in-nigeria-for-mini-importation-business/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 17:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[hotels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:10041/?p=15334</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Mini importation business is a small-scale importation done with little money. It generally involves importing goods from manufacturers or wholesalers authorized to import. It is one of the flexible businesses one can start with a small amount of money and is generally very lucrative. In Nigeria, many vendors are already open to individuals who wish [&#8230;]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Idumota Market, Location, Market Days, Parks and Shipments, Hotels</title>
		<link>https://vocaltravels.com.ng/idumota-market-location-market-days-parks-and-shipments-hotels/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[hotels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:10041/?p=15330</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Idumota Market is a famous market in Lagos that is known for its significant sales of videos and many musical albums. The market is known as one of the oldest markets in Lagos.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Balogun Market, Location, Market Days, Parks and Shipments, Products</title>
		<link>https://vocaltravels.com.ng/balogun-market-location-market-days-parks-and-shipments-products/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[hotels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:10041/?p=15326</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Balogun market is popular in Lagos, Nigeria. The market was created in 2019 near Lagos Island, Nigeria. This market serves as a significant hub for products such as wholesale clothing materials, electronics, jewelry, beverages, oil imports and exports, and so much more. ]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Track Parcel with Parcel Tracking Number – Consider the 5 Comprehensive Steps</title>
		<link>https://vocaltravels.com.ng/how-to-track-parcel-with-parcel-tracking-number/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 13:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[hotels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.geetra.com/?p=15003</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This page “How to Track Parcel with Parcel Tracking Number” discussed the steps to follow to track a parcel when shipped from any Courier agency.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Requirements and Advantages of the Skilled Worker Visa in the UK</title>
		<link>https://vocaltravels.com.ng/skilled-worker-visa-in-the-uk/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 11:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[hotels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.geetra.com/?p=15100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Skilled Worker visa extends an invitation to eligible individuals, beckoning them to the UK to contribute their skills to an approved sponsor in a qualifying role. To qualify for this visa, candidates must amass a total of 70 points, a criterion determined by factors such as skill and salary levels, English language proficiency, and the receipt of a qualifying job offer from a UK employer holding a valid sponsorship license.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Most Affordable Places to Reside in Canada</title>
		<link>https://vocaltravels.com.ng/most-affordable-locations-to-reside-in-canada/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 15:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[hotels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.geetra.com/?p=15040</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To help you get the most bang for your buck, we’ve compiled a list of the most affordable places to live in Canada.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Luxurious Lodge in Tokyo Opening in 2024</title>
		<link>https://vocaltravels.com.ng/best-luxurious-lodge-in-tokyo/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 20:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[hotels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.geetra.com/?p=15034</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Are travelling to Tokyo in 2024? find the best luxurious lodges that give peaceful and wonderful travel experience. In terms of luxurious motels, Tokyo has all the time been in a category by itself. So when Wayne Kask checked into the brand new Bellustar Tokyo, he anticipated a one-of-a-kind expertise. And that is precisely what [&#8230;]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Find US ZIP Code Near Me – Postal Codes Lookup</title>
		<link>https://vocaltravels.com.ng/find-us-zip-code-near-me-postal-codes-lookup/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 13:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[hotels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.geetra.com/?p=15001</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Looking to identify a certain geographic location within the USA, here are US ZIP code lists by state. The US ZIP code is a 5-digit number used to determine certain zones for efficient mail delivery. The United States Postal Service (USPS) and other Parcel and Ship companies used this code to find the actual location in a given geographic space. To find a ZIP Code near me, consider the US ZIP Codes by State below.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arik Air Booking Online – Flight Booking from Arik Airline</title>
		<link>https://vocaltravels.com.ng/arik-air-booking-online-flight-booking-from-arik-airline/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 13:52:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[hotels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.geetra.com/?p=14999</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Are you looking to send your parcel within Nigeria and beyond? Consider the Arik Air Booking Online systems. Arik Airlines is the leading airline in West Africa, with domestic, regional, and international operations. Arik primarily operates from two hubs: the flagship office at Murtala Muhammed International Airport in Lagos and another office at Nnamdi Azikiwe International Airport in Abuja, where it oversees flight services to and from various African destinations.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Send Parcel with UPS &#124; UPS – United States</title>
		<link>https://vocaltravels.com.ng/how-to-send-parcel-with-ups-ups-united-states/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 13:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[hotels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.geetra.com/?p=14997</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you are looking for how to send parcel with UPS in the United States, the process is simple. First Get your parcel ready, get a label for the parcel, and choose an option to send the parcel with UPS. All these processes are listed in this article.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
